{
    "subject": "resource/Nyai_Ahmad_Dahlan",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Yogyakarta",
    "human_readable": "Nyai Ahmad Dahlan was born in Yogyakarta.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8962066173553467,
            "question": "Where was Nyai Ahmad Dahlan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8355633616447449,
            "question": "What are some key events that occurred in Yogyakarta during Nyai Ahmad Dahlan's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8158491849899292,
            "question": "In what century was Nyai Ahmad Dahlan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6594476699829102,
            "question": "What were the major challenges faced by people living in Yogyakarta during Nyai Ahmad Dahlan's time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6297236680984497,
            "question": "What is Nyai Ahmad Dahlan known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32269150018692017,
            "question": "How did Nyai Ahmad Dahlan contribute to Indonesian culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3223455846309662,
            "question": "Who were some influential figures during Nyai Ahmad Dahlan's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3124799132347107,
            "question": "Is Yogyakarta a city in Indonesia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28814926743507385,
            "question": "What role did Nyai Ahmad Dahlan play in Indonesian society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24611826241016388,
            "question": "Can you name any organizations or institutions founded by Nyai Ahmad Dahlan?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nyai Ahmad Dahlan was born in Yogyakarta.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7538_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did Nyai Ahmad Dahlan play in Indonesian society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7538_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Yogyakarta a city in Indonesia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7538_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some influential figures during Nyai Ahmad Dahlan's lifetime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7538_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7538_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7538_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7538_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7538_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7538_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7538_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7538_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7538_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7538_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7538_46.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple is \"Nyai Ahmad Dahlan was born in Yogyakarta.\" Based on the context information, this statement is true. Specifically, documents 1 and 2 mention that Nyai Ahmad Dahlan was born in Yogyakarta, Indonesia.\n\nTherefore, the response should be:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in documents `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7538/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt`, `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7538/re-ranker-msmarco/19.txt`, and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7538/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt`, which all state that Nyai Ahmad Dahlan was born in Yogyakarta, Indonesia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}